closecombattraining.com 2007-11-13

# The Close Combat Company Merchant Policies

Close Combat Training is a division of The Close Combat Company.

The Close Combat Company is the world leader in self-defense training, health and well-being, and the adventure life. Through our brands (Close Combat Training, Close Combat Nutrition, Close Combat Adventure Outpost, Close Combat Fitness and Close Combat Professionals) the Close Combat Company brings you the ideas, insights, inspiration and information you need to live life to the fullest. 

We're a family-run business that treats its customers like family. And we are deeply committed to protecting your privacy and the security of the information you share with us.

We believe you have the right to know everything regarding the information we collect about you ...how this information benefits you...and how you can say "no" to the use of any of this information. 

These policies explain what we do with your information, and what you can expect from the Close Combat Company. By using this site you indicate your acceptance of the Close Combat Company's Privacy Policy and Security Policy; by purchasing any of our products, you indicate your acceptance of the Close Combat Company's Return Policy. 

**Children Under 13:**  
We care about the safety of children. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We encourage you to become involved in your children's online experience, and to share your interest in our sites with your young ones. 

**What information do you collect about me?**  
Close Combat Company collects personal identifying information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us on website(s) and through email. We also collect information during transactions, sponsored events and contests/sweepstakes. When visiting one of our online sites, we collect user-specific information on what pages are visited and volunteered information such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

**What's in it for me?**  
Plenty! The information we collect allows us to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each visitor. Plus, it enables us to notify you about updates to our Web site...contact you with special offers of interest...and customize your Web site experience. In addition, information is shared with reputable organizations who may contact you with special offers of possible interest. 

**What are "cookies" and what do they do for me?**  
In order to provide better service when you return to our site, Close Combat Company may use cookies to store your preferences and information about such things as items added to your shopping cart, purchases you have made with us, what pages you visit, and past activity at a site. "Cookies" are tiny pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are also used to ensure that you are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, to customize Web page content based on your browser type (Netscape or Microsoft Explorer, for example Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. 

If you want to disable cookies, there is a simple procedure in most Internet browsers that allow you to turn off cookies. Please remember however, that cookies may be required to allow you to use certain features of our sites. 

We may also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here 

**With whom do you share information about me?**  
From time to time, we make our customer e-mail addresses, postal addresses and telephone numbers available to other reputable businesses whose products or services might be of value to you. If you do not want us to share your information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by accessing the form at privacy@Close Combat Company.com, by calling us at 917-546-6870, or writing to us at Customer Service, Close Combat Company, 1000C Lake St. Ramsey, NJ 07446. We retain email opt-out and postal/telephone non solicitation requests for 5 years. 

**Transfers of Information for Legal Purposes**  
Close Combat Company, Inc. may need to disclose certain information to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, search warrant, in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a law enforcement agency request. If there is a change of control in Close Combat Company's business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), or a sale or transfer of its assets, customer information could be sold or transferred as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially used by the Purchaser or other recipient of said customer information. 

**Links**  
Close Combat Company sites may, on occasion, contain links to other sites with information gathering practices different from our own. Visitors should consult privacy policies for all other sites as Close Combat Company has no control over information submitted to or collected by such third parties. 

Close Combat Company sites sometimes offer contest, sweepstakes or promotions sponsored or co-sponsored by third parties. These third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. Close Combat Company has no control over the third party sponsor's use of this information. The Close Combat Company site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third party sponsors will be provided access to such information. 

**What if I don't want e-mail from Close Combat Company?**  
Easy. If you do not want to receive e-mail from Close Combat Company, please let us know by either utilizing the unsubscribe link available on email communications, accessing the form at <http://www.closecombatcompany.com/privacy.php>, calling us at 917-546-6870, or writing to us at: Customer Service, Close Combat Company, 1000C Lake St. Ramsey, NJ 07446.  We retain all such email opt-out requests for 5 years. 

**May I see the information you collect about me?**  
Yes! Upon request, we provide our customers with access to personal account information (e.g., customer number)...account status (outstanding balance)...and contact information (i.e., name, address, phone number). You may receive a copy of your information via email by completing the form at <http://www.closecombatcompany.com/privacy.php>, or you may call us at 917-546-6870. 

In addition, we offer web visitors the ability to correct any inaccuracies in their contact information, simply by accessing the appropriate Customer Service site, completing the form at <http://www.closecombatcompany.com/privacy.php>, or by calling us at (800) 914-9363. If you prefer, you may write to us at Customer Service, Close Combat Company, 1000C Lake St. Ramsey, NJ 07446. 

**Changes...**  
Close Combat Company may need to change this privacy policy from time to time in order to address new issues, evolving technologies, changes on our sites or business practices. Close Combat Company will post those changes so you will always know what information we gather and how we might use that information. Please refer back to this policy regularly. 

**What about data security?**  
To ensure the security of your data- including address information and credit card numbers- Close Combat Company always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. 

**Rules for Submissions and Messages**  
Responsibility for what is posted in the discussion groups or other public forums lies with each user--you alone are responsible for the content of your messages, and the consequences of any such messages. We cannot and do not review every submission a user may make. We neither endorse nor guarantee the accuracy or propriety of any submission. We do, however, reserve the right but do not assume the obligation to restrict or prohibit your use of our sites if we believe you are violating any of the terms of the agreement and to remove, edit, or relocate any submission as we see fit whether for legal or other reasons. 

**Member Conduct**  
You understand that all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that you, and not Close Combat Company, Inc., are entirely responsible for all Content that you upload, post or otherwise transmit. Close Combat Company does not control the Content posted and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. You understand that by using a Close Combat Company site, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable. 

You agree to not use the Close Combat Company sites in order to:

  * upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;
  * harm minors in any way;
  * impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a Close Combat Company official, forum leader, guide or host, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
  * forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any Content transmitted through the Service or develop restricted or password-only access pages, or hidden pages or images (those not linked to from another accessible page);
  * upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that you do not have a right to transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements);
  * upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party;
  * upload, post or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation, except in those areas of the Service that are designated for such purpose;
  * upload, post or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;
  * interfere with or disrupt the servers or networks connected to the Close Combat Company site, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the site;
  * intentionally or unintentionally violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, including, but not limited to, regulations promulgated by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, any rules of any national or other securities exchange, including, without limitation, the New York Stock Exchange, the American Stock Exchange or the NASDAQ, and any regulations having the force of law;
  * "stalk" or otherwise harass another;
  * collect or store personal data about other users;
  * promote or provide instructional information about illegal activities, promote physical harm or injury against any group or individual, or promote any act of cruelty to animals.
  * use your home page (or directory) as storage for remote loading or as a door or signpost to another home page
  * engage in commercial activities without the express written consent of Close Combat Company, Inc. This includes, but is not limited to, the following activities:

  * offering for sale any products or services;
  * soliciting for advertisers or sponsors;
  * conducting raffles or contests that require any type of entry fee;
  * displaying a sponsorship banner of any kind, including those that are generated by banner or link exchange services
  * displaying banners for services that provide cash or cash-equivalent prizes to users in exchange for hyperlinks to their web sites. 

**Rights**  
You acknowledge that we acquire all Rights to use any posted materials as described above so that we do not violate any Rights you may have in materials you post. By submitting content to or through our sites, you grant us the non-exclusive right to reproduce, modify and distribute it as we see fit in any medium and for any purpose in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed. You also permit any other user to access, display, and print such content for personal use. You vouch that any material you submit does not violate, plagiarize or infringe upon the right of any third party, including copyright, trademark or proprietary rights. If non-original content is included in your posting, you must obtain permission from the content owner and attribute it. 

**We appreciate the opportunity to serve you!**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy statement or if you feel that this site has not followed its stated information policy, feel free to contact us. Our postal address is: 1000C Lake St. Ramsey, NJ 07446 and we can be reached via e-mail at: info@CloseCombatCompany.com. You can reach us by telephone at 917-546-6870. 

Additionally, you may contact your state or local consumer protection office, The Direct Marketing Association's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, the Better Business Bureau, or The Federal Trade Commission by phone at (202) FTC-HELP (202/382-4357) and online at www.ftc.gov. 

Note: This privacy policy applies to all of Close Combat Company's owned and operated websites and to Close Combat Company's other information gathering activities. 

Close Combat Company complies with all the stringent standards of ethical conduct set forth by the Direct Marketing Association.
